420links.co.uk 2018-09-01

# PRIVACY-COOKIE

**420links Privacy Policy**

420links is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement outlines what information we gather about you when you visit 420links websites and explains how we use that information. 420links policy is to keep your personal information which we receive through our websites completely confidential. The information will be used for internal processing and functional purposes only. We will never share or sell any personal information with other parties.

Collection of your Personal Information: The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, address, e-mail, phone. We may collect certain information about your visit, such as the type of browser you use; the date and time you had access to our websites; the pages that you accessed while at our websites and the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our websites. This information is used to help improve our websites and maintain optimal functionality of the websites.

Use of your Personal Information: The personal information collected on our websites will be used to provide the services you have requested which includes but is not limited to third party payment providers like PayPal and shipping services like TNT, UPS or FedEx. We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, we may send you information about 420links.

Use of Cookies on the 420links websites

The 420links websites use some unobtrusive cookies to store information on your computer. What is a cookie? A cookie is a small file that is placed on your computer. Cookies make it possible to add basic and advanced functionality to a website. Among other things, cookies enable the log-in process, as well as the collection of anonymous web-statistics.

The cookies that are used on our websites, cannot be used by 420links to identify you personally, no personal data is collected in these cookies. Additionally, these cookies cannot be used to identify you on any third party website.

Important Note: Some functionality we offer through our websites like our social media intergration requires third party involvement for it to work, services providers like Facebook may also place cookies on your computer, it is important that you are also aware of the privacy policy and the use of cookies of these service providers.

Web-Statistics: 420links uses web-statistics which allows us to analyze data in regards to visitor movement on our websites to further improve the user experience and service. Under no circumstances is this data used for any other purposes.

Disable Cookies: All modern browsers have cookies enabled by default simply because most websites and especially webshops will not work without them. They can be disabled by changing the settings of your browser. Please note that by doing so you will not be able to use most modern websites, including the 420links websites.

This policy is subject to occasional change, visit this page every time you make use of our websites incase any changes have been made. Please redirect any questions which you might have in regards to our privacy policy and or the use of cookies on our websites to our customer support team through our contact form

This policy has not changed since 29-04-2015
